Aibangbe Victor

Web Developer

Nigeria

3 +234 813 955 2920

Personal Statement

Industry expert in Web Development, self-motivated web developer with five years of comprehensive experience managing multiple clients. Gained project based training from ALX academy and only project challenge platforms like Front-end mentor, some of this project are available on my personal portfolio website. Passionate and hardworking to deliver on deadlines. Strong HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, DMBS, and PYTHON programmer. I will be able to create a strategic approach for brand awareness to beat competition thereby generating more leads for products or services.

Work Experience

Web Developer. 2023 - Till Date

FREELANCER

Video Editor. 2020 - 2023

SAVCLICK

Editing creating high definition and lead audience engaging videos. These videos include captured footages, 2d explainer video, website navigation video, cryptocurrency and forex video, and general branded video production. Render this video for the company's growth and satisfaction of her client(s)

Accomplishments:

- * Produced videos and its audio using Adobe Creative Suite and Text To Speech softwares.
- * Social Media posting of Video contents along with the Social Media Management team
- *Monthly report of media created for the company.

Member 2019 - 2020

National Youth Service Corp (NYSC)

Served in the State Ministry of Science and Technology, Enugu State, Nigeria, under the ICT department during my one year National Service program.

Accomplishment:

- Worked alongside the ICT director and other Corp members to troubleshoot and fix computer system in the ministry.
- Use Microsoft Office programs to carry out tasks during my service year.

Computer Hardware and Software Technician

Education

Certificate in Intro to Software Engineering Holberton School (ALX)	2023 - 2024
Certification in Copy Writing For Conversions Alison Online Course	2020
Diploma in Social Media Strategy Alison Online Course	2020
Bachelor of Engineering, Computer Engineering University	2013 – 2018
ICT Trainee SIWES Program	2017
WAEC Certificate in Science High School	2006 – 2012
School Leaving Certificate Primary School	2000 – 2006

Personal Attributes

- Excellent team work ability
- Goal oriented
- Self-motivated and result Oriented
- Sound in numeric and analytical issues
- Possesses excellent interpersonal communication
- Problem solver
- Honest and creative

Hobbies

- Reading
- Gym
- Playing Soccer
- Computing
- Coding

Reference

LinkedIn www.google.com